<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project on Flavio M Conde</title>
    <link>https://flaviomconde.github.io/Portafolio_DataAnalyst1/in/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project on Flavio M Conde</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>in</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://flaviomconde.github.io/Portafolio_DataAnalyst1/in/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Proyecto III: ETL y Analisis de Datos (SQL&#43;Power BI)</title>
      <link>https://flaviomconde.github.io/Portafolio_DataAnalyst1/in/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://flaviomconde.github.io/Portafolio_DataAnalyst1/in/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Currently developing it&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project II: Analysis of financial market prices</title>
      <link>https://flaviomconde.github.io/Portafolio_DataAnalyst1/in/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://flaviomconde.github.io/Portafolio_DataAnalyst1/in/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>We were hired by a company that seeks to invest in the stock market and asks you to analyze it in detail. Considering that the company does not know this financial area, it requests an explanation of what has happened in this market in recent years (considering positive and negative impacts since 2000), investment recommendations (whether focused on companies or sectors of these) and other complementary information that, as data experts, we are able to provide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project I: Recommendation System</title>
      <link>https://flaviomconde.github.io/Portafolio_DataAnalyst1/in/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://flaviomconde.github.io/Portafolio_DataAnalyst1/in/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Starting from the context of the life cycle of a Machine Learning project, we must consider everything from the processing and collection of data (Data Engineer stuff) to the training and maintenance of the ML model as new data arrives. First, perform specific transformations on the data (ETL) to make it available through endpoints accessible through the API that was deployed in Render. Secondly, perform an EDA process on the data to build a movie recommendation system with machine learning.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
